<branch name="string">
specifies a branch with name NAME.

<changebranch newbranch="string"/>
ChangeBranchCommand that switches branch to NEWBRANCH.

<addcharacter name="string" (optional)animations="string" (optional)sound="string"/>
CharacterAddCommand that adds character with name NAME, animations named ANIMATIONS, and speaking sound SOUND.

<setanimation name="string" animation="string" wait="boolean"/>
CharacterAnimationCommand that sets character NAME to have animation ANIMATION. Waits to go on to next command iff WAIT.

<setdirection name="string" direction="int"/>
CharacterDirectionCommand that sets character NAME to have direction DIRECTION.

<setname name="string" newname="string"/>
CharacterNameCommand that sets character NAME to have display name NEWNAME.

<setposition name="string" position="string"/>
CharacterPositionCommand that sets character NAME to have the position mapped to POSITION.

<setvisible name="string" visible="boolean"/>
CharacterVisibleCommand that sets character NAME to have visibility VISIBLE.

<sequence>
    <command/>
    <command/>
    <command/>
</sequence>
CommandSequence with a series of COMMANDS.

<debug message="string"/>
DebugCommand that prints MESSAGE.

<message speaker="string" (optional)wait="boolean">
    <assign name="string">
        <command/>
    </assign>
    ...
    <text>
    ...
</message>
Message command spoken by character named SPEAKER, assigns commands to shortcuts
to be used in text, and displays text as separate windows. WAIT is true by default
and determines if player input is necessary to proceed to the next command.

<playmusic name="string" loop="boolean"/>
PlayMusicCommand that plays music with name NAME and sets looping to LOOP.

<pausemusic/>
PlayMusicCommand that pauses music.

<resumemusic/>
PlayMusicCommand that resumes music.

<playsound name="string"/>
PlaySoundCommand that plays sound with name NAME.

<preload > #TODO

<choices>
    <choice name="string">
        (optional)<if ...> script </if>
        <command/>
    </choice>
    <choice name="string">
        <command/>
    </choice>
</choices>
ShowChoicesCommand with text array of each choices NAME and command array of the commands. When a choice
has an <if> inside of it, it's only added if the SCRIPT evaluates to a true value.

<delay time="float"/>
DelayCommand with delay time TIME.

<textspeed time="integer"/>
TextSpeedCommand with waiting time TIME.

<script language="language" (optional)isfile="boolean">
    code or file
</script>
ExecuteScriptCommand that executes the code or contents of the file (if isfile) in LANGUAGE.

<init language="language">
    name value
    name value
    name value
</init>
VariableInitializeCommand that initializes the variables of language LANGUAGE to VALUEs
if they have not yet been defined.

<if language="language" (optional)isfile="boolean">
    script
    <command/>
    <command/>
    <command/>
</if>
VariableConditionCommand that executes COMMANDS if the SCRIPT results in a true value when executed.
LANGUAGE is the scripting language being used and ISFILE determines whether a file should be loaded named SCRIPT.






